defloration.com 2019-06-24

# Defloration - photos and video. Privacy statement

Effective May 16, 2018

This Privacy Policy (the “Policy”) describes data collection and use practices associated with websites of Quicksol GmbH (the “Sites”). Quicksol GmbH is a company registered in Austria with company registration number FN401214x and having its registered office address at Neustiftgasse 107, Top-1, 1070, Vienna, Austria. This Policy explains what information we collect about you and what we do with it. We reserve the right to modify this Policy at any time, and we will notify you of any material changes to the Policy by posting the new Policy here and changing the “Effective Date” at the top. We encourage you to check this page periodically for any changes. By using or navigating our Sites, you acknowledge that you have read, understand and agree to be bound by this Policy or any modified Policy as posted. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not use or visit any of the Sites or any portion of the Sites.

Personal information collected on and/or through the Sites is stored and processed in the EU (Austria, The Netherlands and Hungary) and by using any aspect of the Sites, you consent to the transfer of information outside of your country to Austria, The Netherlands, Hungary and to other countries.

We do not collect or store any credit card information. The credit card details of our customers are processed by our Payment Service Provider – [VirtualXS](https://vxs.com/) (Virtual Access Internet B.V. is a company registered in The Netherlands and having its registered office address at Anna van Renesseplein 8, 1911 KN, Uitgeest, The Netherlands). All credit card transactions processed by VirtualXS are subject to the VirtualXS 's Privacy Policy.

Quicksol GmbH may instruct third party operators to undertake processing activities relating to the personal information of users of the Sites.

### INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USAGE

We collect and use your information in order to fulfill your orders and/or requests, to facilitate your viewing and use of our Sites, to communicate with you, and to provide you with information about our Sites, as well as some of our partners and third party companies in which we think you may be interested. We also use this information to compile broad demographic and Site usage information about our users in general that does not contain anything that could be used to identify you personally. Besides our own tools we also use Google Analytics to collect and process demographic and Site usage information.

We use information collected to evaluate and improve our services. We may develop and use, in our sole discretion, consumer research, which may be based on your use of our services.

### PERSONAL INFORMATION COLLECTED BY QUICKSOL GmbH

To use, purchase a product or service online, Quicksol GmbH may request that you voluntarily supply your Personal Information. Personal Information we collect and it’s use are as follows:

#### Log information

When you use our Sites, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, IP address, the date and time of your request. This information is stored in our system for a short time, usually less than 48 hours.

When you access your membership account on our Sites our server records your login-name, the time of your log in and your IP address. This data is stored in our system for one year.

#### User communications

If you send us an e-mail we store your e-mail address. If you send us a message through a contact-form on our Sites besides your e-mail address we also store your IP address and the User-Agent: header of your browser. We may retain email, mail or any other communication to us in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services.

#### Registration and/or order information

When you sign up for our service or purchase any merchandise from us, all transaction information is processed by our Payment Service Provider VirtualXS but for accounting purposes we store the purchase details (except card details) for at least 5 years. This includes your name, address, username, email address and transaction information (except card details) like, but not limited to, transaction amount, description of the goods or services purchased. If you order a DVD or any other tangible item from us we store the shipping address provided with your order.

Quicksol GmbH does not keep this data any longer than it’s strictly necessary for the purposes it was provided for and/or we are legally obliged to.

#### Use of Contact information

We may use the contact information provided by you upon registration or order to notify you about changes to our services and provide you with information that is relevant to your use of our Sites.  
We may use the e-mail address provided by you upon registration or order to send you advertising and may use third-party operators to send marketing e-mails. You have at any time the opportunity to unsubscribe from our marketing e-mails using the link in the marketing message or contacting us through the contact-forms on our Sites.

### INFORMATION SHARING

We may share information we collect with third party service providers to manage certain aspects of the Site and/or the services we provide, such as maintaining our servers and processing or fulfilling orders for products and services you purchase through the Site.

We may share your e-mail address with third party service providers to send you marketing e-mails.

We may also disclose your information in special cases if required to do so by law, court order or governmental authority or when we believe in good faith that disclosing this information is otherwise necessary or advisable, including, for instance, to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interfering with the rights or property of Quicksol GmbH.

In the event of a change in ownership or a merger with, acquisition by, or sale of assets to another entity we reserve the right to transfer all user information collected in connection with the Site, including but not limited to email addresses, to a separate entity.

### USE OF COOKIES

Cookies are pieces of information generated by web servers and stored on your computer for future access. The Sites use cookie technology to enhance your online experience by making the Sites easier to navigate or to make a feature work better. The Sites also use cookies to track purchases made through our affiliate partners. Generally, cookies can be disabled at your discretion.

However, you must accept cookies in order for certain parts of the Sites to work. In addition, while you may always opt-out of receiving cookies, please note that your opt-out choices are device-specific and browser-specific, so if your preference is to opt out, you will need to do it for each of your devices and browsers.

Google Analytics also uses cookies for analytical purposes. Please, read Google’s Privacy Policy.

### INFORMATION SECURITY

Quicksol GmbH takes reasonable precautions to maintain the security of any information obtained from and about you and to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of information under our control. The personally identifiable information held by Quicksol GmbH is stored in a secure location with limited administrative access.

### THIRD PARTY SITES

The Site may contain links to other websites. By clicking on any banner advertisement or other link, you will be redirected off the Site and to the applicable third party website. Quicksol GmbH is not responsible for the privacy policies or content of such websites. You should make sure that you read and understand the privacy policies of these sites and direct any concerns regarding external links to the site administrator or webmaster of that third party website.

### USE OF THE SERVICES BY CHILDREN

Our services are not intended for persons under the age of 18. By using our Sites, you hereby represent that you are at least 18 years old. Quicksol GmbH does not knowingly collect any personal information from persons under the age of 18.

### YOUR RIGHTS

Under the General Data Protection Regulation you have a number of important rights. In summary, those include rights to:  
access to your personal data and to certain other supplementary information that this Policy is already designed to address; require Us to correct any mistakes in your information which We hold; require the erasure of personal data concerning you in certain situations; receive the personal data concerning you which you have provided to Us, in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format and have the right to transmit those data to a third party in certain situations; object at any time to processing of personal data concerning you for direct marketing; object to decisions being taken by automated means which produce legal effects concerning you or similarly significantly affect you; object in certain other situations to our continued processing of your personal data; otherwise restrict our processing of your personal data in certain circumstances.

If you would like to exercise any of those rights, please:  
contact us using a contact-form on one of our Sites, let Us have enough information to identify you, let Us have proof of your identity and address. Where you are a user of our services you should email us from the email address that you used to register on our Sites. (To identify you we may request additional information from you);  
and let Us know the information to which your request relates.

All marketing e-mails you receive from us will include specific instructions on how to unsubscribe, and you may unsubscribe at any time. Additionally, you have the option to remove your information from our database by sending us a message through the contact-forms on our Sites.

You may correct or update the personal information you have provided to Quicksol GmbH by sending us a message through the contact-forms on our Sites.

We hope that We can resolve any query or concern you raise about our use of your information but The General Data Protection Regulation also gives you right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority, in particular in the European Union (or European Economic Area) state where you work, normally live or where any alleged infringement of data protection laws occurred. The supervisory authority in Austria is Datenschutzbehördethe.

### CONTACT US

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices of our Site, please contact us through the contact-forms on our Sites.
